<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Tech Index</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Tech Index</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.150.0</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 15:16:59 +0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Use the New Whatsapp Secret Code Feature for Locked Chats</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/tutorials/how-to-use-the-new-whatsapp-secret-code-feature-for-locked-chats/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 15:16:59 +0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/tutorials/how-to-use-the-new-whatsapp-secret-code-feature-for-locked-chats/</guid>
      <description>WhatsApp&amp;#39;s secret code hides locked chats completely—type it in search to unlock. Android/iOS steps inside, plus PK tweaks for slow nets. No more nosy eyes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Deploy a Static Website to GitHub Pages for Free</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/tutorials/how-to-deploy-a-static-website-to-github-pages-for-free/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/tutorials/how-to-deploy-a-static-website-to-github-pages-for-free/</guid>
      <description>A step-by-step guide on deploying static websites to GitHub Pages without spending a dime, covering setup, configuration, and common pitfalls for beginners and pros alike.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Clear Cache and Cookies on Every Major Browser (2025 Guide)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/tutorials/clear-cache-and-cookies-on-every-major-browser/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/tutorials/clear-cache-and-cookies-on-every-major-browser/</guid>
      <description>Complete 2025 guide to clearing cache and cookies on Chrome, Firefox, Safari, Edge, and more. Step-by-step instructions for desktop and mobile with troubleshooting tips to fix site glitches, improve performance, and boost privacy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using ChatGPT for Automating Your Daily Mail Sending Process</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/tutorials/using-chatgpt-for-automating-your-daily-mail-sending-process/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 13:36:41 +0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/tutorials/using-chatgpt-for-automating-your-daily-mail-sending-process/</guid>
      <description>A detailed guide on using ChatGPT to automate your daily email workflow, saving time and increasing productivity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello and welcome to &lt;strong&gt;Tech Index&lt;/strong&gt;, the ultimate source for valuable tech tutorials and SaaS resources. Here at Tech Index, our focus is on the simple: making the complex world of modern software development and gadgetry simple and accessible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;who-we-are&#34;&gt;Who We Are&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are a committed team of senior software architects, developers, and tech enthusiasts who strongly believe in the importance of accessible, accurate, and feasible education in this technological space, having a collective experience of many decades in this space and understanding the implications of learning so many different technological stacks and tools in this space.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact Us</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/contact/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We look forward to hearing your feedback and are ready to answer any questions that you may have about our tutorials or services.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;get-in-touch&#34;&gt;Get in Touch&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For general inquiries, technical assistance, and collaboration requests, kindly send your emails to:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:e.net.lectures.01@gmail.com&#34;&gt;e.net.lectures.01@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;response-time&#34;&gt;Response Time&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our team checks all the messages we receive. We always strive to respond to all specific inquiries within &lt;strong&gt;48 hours&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In your email, please provide as many details as possible, such as the name of the tutorial or error message. This helps us guide you better.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disclaimer</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/disclaimer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/disclaimer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last updated: December 23, 2025&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The information provided by Tech Index (&amp;ldquo;we&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;us&amp;rdquo;, or &amp;ldquo;our&amp;rdquo;) on 
http://localhost:1313/ (the &amp;ldquo;Site&amp;rdquo;) is for general informational purposes only. All information on the Site is provided in good faith, however we make no representation or warranty of any kind, express or implied, regarding the accuracy, adequacy, validity, reliability, availability, or completeness of any information on the Site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;professional-disclaimer&#34;&gt;Professional Disclaimer&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Site cannot and does not contain software development or legal advice. The technical information is provided for general informational and educational purposes only and is not a substitute for professional advice. Accordingly, before taking any actions based upon such information, we encourage you to consult with the appropriate professionals. We do not provide any kind of software development or legal advice. THE USE OR RELIANCE OF ANY INFORMATION CONTAINED ON THE SITE IS SOLELY AT YOUR OWN RISK.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/privacy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last updated: December 23, 2025&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tech Index, accessible from &lt;code&gt;
http://localhost:1313/&lt;/code&gt;, has one of its major priorities being the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is gathered and recorded by Tech Index and how we use it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;log-files&#34;&gt;Log Files&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tech Index follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this and a part of hosting services&amp;rsquo; analytics. The information collected by log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users&amp;rsquo; movement on the website, and gathering demographic information.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terms of Service</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/terms/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last updated: December 23, 2025&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The use of this website assumes your acceptance of these terms and conditions. You should NOT use Tech Index if you do NOT agree to abide by all that is stated within these terms and conditions on this page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;license&#34;&gt;License&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If not otherwise indicated, the intellectual property rights to the contents of the Tech Index lie with the Tech Index and/or with the licensors of the Tech Index. All rights to the said property rights are hereby reserved. But you can access the same from the Tech Index and use the same solely for your purpose.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
